{
  "response": [
    {
      "question": "What does the Acronym REST Stand for?",
      "option1": "Representational State Transform",
      "option2": "Representational State Transfer",
      "option3": "Represent State Transform",
      "option4": "Represent State Transfer",
      "answer": "Representational State Transfer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the protocol used in REST?",
      "option1": "FTP",
      "option2": "HTTP",
      "option3": "JMX",
      "option4": "SOAP",
      "answer": "HTTP"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the HTTP Status Code Related to Page Not Found?",
      "option1": "402",
      "option2": "403",
      "option3": "401",
      "option4": "404",
      "answer": "404"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the HTTP Code Related to Internal Server Error?",
      "option1": "500",
      "option2": "501",
      "option3": "504",
      "option4": "502",
      "answer": "500"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the HTTP Code 200 Indicate?",
      "option1":  "Error",
      "option2": "Completed",
      "option3":"Success",
      "option4":  "Warning",
      "answer": "Success"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which HTTP method do we use to make an HTTP request to create a new resource?",
      "option1":  "POST",
      "option2":  "PUT",
      "option3":  "GET",
      "option4": "CREATE",
      "answer": "POST"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which HTTP method do we use to make an HTTP request to update an existing resource?",
       "option1":  "POST",
      "option2":  "PUT",
      "option3":  "UPDATE",
      "option4": "DELETE",
      "answer": "PUT"
    },
    {
      "question": "Choose the correct URI format to get a sub-resource by resource id and sub-resource id",
      "option1":  "/{resource}/{resource-id}/{sub-resource}/{sub-resource-id}",
      "option2":  "/{resource}/{sub-resource}/{sub-resource-id}",
      "option3":  "{sub-resource}/{sub-resource-id}/{resource}/{resource-id}",
      "option4": "/{resource}/{resource-id}/{sub-resource-id}/{sub-resource}",
      "answer": "/{resource}/{resource-id}/{sub-resource}/{sub-resource-id}"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is not REST Architectural Constraints?",
      "option1": "Client-Server",
      "option2":"Stateless",
      "option3": "Cacheable",
      "option4":"Service orchestration",
      "answer": "Service orchestration"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the HTTP status code 201 indicate?",
      "option1":  "OK",
      "option2":  "Created",
      "option3":  "Accepted",
      "option4": "No Content",
      "answer":  "Created"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following component of HTTP request indicates HTTP methods such as GET, POST, DELETE, PUT etc.?",
      "option1":  "VERB",
      "option2":  "URI",
      "option3":  "HTTP Version",
      "option4": "Request Header",
      "answer":  "VERB"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following HTTP method should be idempotent in nature?",
      "option1":  "GET",
      "option2": "PUT",
      "option3":"POST",
      "option4":  "HEAD",
      "answer": "PUT"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following HTTP method should be used to get status of method availability in RESTful web service?",
       "option1":  "GET",
      "option2": "PUT",
      "option3":"OPTIONS",
      "option4":  "HEAD",
      "answer": "HEAD"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is correct about JAX-RS?",
     "option1":  "AX-RS makes heavy use of annotations available from Java SE 5 to simplify development of JAVA based web services creation and deployment",
      "option2":  "It also provides supports for creating clients for RESTful web services.",
      "option3":  "Both of the above",
      "option4": "None of the above.",
      "answer":  "Both of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "Status/Response Code - Indicate Server status for the requested resource.",
     "option1":  "false",
      "option2":  "true",
      "option3":  "-",
      "option4": "-",
      "answer":  "true"
    },
    {
      "question": "RESTful web services make use of FTP protocol as a medium of communication between client and server.",
    "option1":  "false",
      "option2":  "true",
      "option3":  "-",
      "option4": "-",
      "answer":  "false"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following annotation of JAX RS API states the HTTP Response generated by web service?",
     "option1":  "@DELETE",
      "option2":  "@HEAD",
      "option3":  "@Produces",
      "option4": "@Consumes",
      "answer":  "@Produces"
    }
  ]
}